millionpictures.co 2016-04-02

# Privacy Policy - Million Pictures

### Your privacy is critically important to us. At Automattic we have a few fundamental principles:

This is Million Pictures privacy policy. This document explains Million Pictures policies for the collection, use and disclosure of personal information. Million Pictures abides by applicable privacy legislation.

Million Pictures provides social photo community and entertainment website.

**The Information we collect**

Million Pictures collects information by various methods including information actively provided by its customers, and tools such as cookies to enhance the user’s website experience.

The types of personal information we collect include the user’s name and contact information, IP address, as well as any information you voluntarily post on the website. Million Pictures also collects personal information about users from various social media or other sites that the user identifies with, but only to the extent that users have given their permission to those sites to share such information. Information collected from such sites may include, without limitation, interests, friends, birthday, city, and likes.

**How we use this information**

This information is used to provide our web based services.

Million Pictures may use aggregate or anonymous information which will not be linked to identify individuals for various other uses for itself and third parties.

**Who we share this information with**

Million Pictures does not share personal information with any third parties except as disclosed in this policy. Million Pictures may provide personal information to its consultants, subcontractors and professional advisers (which shall be bound by privacy obligations) to assist Million Pictures uses disclosed herein.

If at any time we wish to disclose personal information to third parties for that third party’s use, we will obtain your explicit permission. If you do grant such permission, you may revoke it at any time.

Our websites contain links to third party sites where you may purchase items. Million Pictures makes commissions from those sales, and does some tracking so the third party knows what site you came from, but Million Pictures does not provide your personal information to the third party.

**Advertisers**

Each time you visit a Million Pictures website, third party advertisers and advertising companies, including Google, may collect personal and other information, through your IP address, and by using technology such as cookies. Advertisements appearing on the website are delivered to you by third party advertisers, often based on what you do on various websites. This is sometimes referred to as behavioral advertising, or contextual advertising. Third party advertisers and advertising companies use information about you (not including your name or email address), including your IP address and cookies collected through your use of websites, to provide advertisements on this website about goods and services that may be of interest to you. The use of this information collected by third party advertisers and advertising companies through this website is not covered by this privacy policy and Million Pictures is not responsible for the use of this information by third parties.

You may opt out of the use of Google’s cookies for interest-based advertising by visiting the Google ads preference manager on the Google website. You may opt out of Google and other third-party’s use of cookies and other similar technology for interest-based advertising.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies. 

**Your Privacy Choices**

Users may post information on the website (user registration may be required), which you may or may not want to share with certain other users. Users may make privacy choices by selecting options here. Your default privacy settings will be the most privacy friendly settings with the least sharing. Users should keep the privacy choices they have made in mind and avoid posting information they do not want to be shared in light of those choices. User information is retained by Million Pictures for as long as you maintain a login ID and profile, and for a period of up to 2 years after you terminate your profile. Users may however choose to terminate their profile and require Million Pictures to delete all their personal information.

**Security**

Personal information is protected by security measures appropriate to the nature of the information.

**Accessing information**

If an individual believes that any of their personal information on the website is inaccurate, and it is information that the user cannot change, you can contact Million Pictures privacy officer to request appropriate corrections.

**General**

Million Pictures may amend this policy from time to time by posting an updated version on our website. If such amendments affect how Million Pictures uses or discloses personal information already held by Million Pictures in a material way, Million Pictures will obtain consent.

This policy was last updated on August 10, 2015.

Notwithstanding the general terms of this policy, the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information may be made outside of the terms herein to the extent provided for in any applicable privacy or other legislation in effect from time to time, or pursuant to court orders.

Million Pictures may disclose personal information to another entity purchasing (including for diligence purposes prior to purchase) the assets of Million Pictures, provided that entity abides by this or a similar privacy policy.

**Contact us**

For more information on Million Pictures and privacy please contact at: [contact@millionpictures.co](mailto:contact@millionpictures.co)
